[Log In](https://builtwith.com/login) · [Signup for Free](https://builtwith.com/signup)

* [Tools](javascript:void(0))

* [Features](javascript:void(0))

* [Resources](javascript:void(0))

 Lookup

1. [Home](https://builtwith.com/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

**PRIVACY POLICY AS DATA PROCESSOR**  
  
Effective: 1st May 2018  
Last Updated:8th February 2024  
  
This privacy policy applies to builtwith.com owned and operated by BuiltWith Pty Ltd ("BuiltWith","we","us","our"). This privacy policy describes how BuiltWith collects, uses, shares and secures personal information you provide. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.  

TL;DR  
  
We collect and store your email address if you consent to us doing that. We store it securely and have a few third parties that need to see that data for email deliverability, fraud prevention and payment processing.  

DIRECT COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA  
  
The personal data you provide to BuiltWith directly is your email address. It will be processed for the following purposes only:  
  
    a.  To provide BuiltWith mandatory account status emails (password reset, email verification, welcome email etc...)  
    b.  To identify you when you login to our website.  
    c.  To receive marketing emails from us (optional consent opt-in).  
  
We may also collect and store your address, if you provide it to us for invoicing purposes only.  
  
The processing of data for the purpose above will be carried out via automated electronic means only.  

FAILURE TO PROVIDE CONSENT  
  
The provision of consent is optional. However failure to provide consent for a. and b. above will render it impossible to use BuiltWith internet services as we require your email to allow you to login and enable your account.  

COOKIE POLICY  
  
We use cookies for the prevention of automated data access scraping bot prevention.  
  
Our website uses cookies to allow us to identify you when you have logged in to your account.  

| Cookie Name | Description |
| --- | --- |
| BWSSON | Encrypted cookie identifying your account. |
| BWSTATE | Current session identification cookie. |

We embed videos from Vimeo, they might set cookies; view their cookie policy here - https://vimeo.com/cookie\_policy  
  
We allow authentication Amazon they might set cookies; view their cookie policy here - https://aws.amazon.com/legal/cookies/  
  
We allow authentication Google they might set cookies; view their cookie policy here - https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies  
  
We embed maps from MapBox they might set cookies; view their cookie policy here - https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy  
  
You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block our cookies you will not be able to login to BuiltWith.  

SERVICE PROVIDER THIRD PARTIES WHO MAY PROCESS YOUR DIRECT PERSONAL DATA  
  
Our sharing of your personal data is very limited and a requirement for us to operate BuiltWith. All third parties are listed below.  
  
The email addresses that provide consent will be processed by 3rd party email delivery service provider Postmark. See their privacy page here - https://postmarkapp.com/eu-privacy  
  
If you sign up for payment with credit card and/or PayPal your personal details will be processed by Braintree/PayPal, see their privacy policy here - https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full  
  
If you sign up for payment with credit card you can optionally enable your account using our "know your customer" automated process provided by Persona, see their privacy policy here - https://withpersona.com/legal/privacy-policy  
  
If you sign up for payments with PayPal or credit card your PII may be stored in our accounting system Xero, see their privacy policy here - https://www.xero.com/au/legal/privacy/  
  
If you sign up for payments with Cryptocurrency through Coinbase your email may be processed by Coinbase, see their privacy policy here - https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy?locale=en  
  
If you sign up for payments with Cryptocurrency through CoinPayments your email may be processed by CoinPayments, see their privacy policy here - https://www.coinpayments.net/help-privacy  
  
If you choose to authenticate with Google you data may be processed by Alphabet Inc, see their privacy policy here - https://policies.google.com/privacy  
  
If you choose to authenticate with Amazon you data may be processed by Amazon Inc, see their privacy policy here - https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/  
  
In certain situations, BuiltWith Pty Ltd may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, when we believe there is a violation to our [terms](https://builtwith.com/terms), protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request  

INDIRECT COLLECTION AND PROCESS OF PERSONAL DATA  
  
Indirectly we will collect your IP address based on the system you use to access our website via our secure web servers logging system. We collect this information for the purposes of detecting and preventing fraud and unauthorized access and maintaining the security of our systems. We will use but not collect/store your geolocation based on your IP address to personalize your experience of using the BuiltWith website.  
  
We use Google reCAPTCHA for fraud prevention which may collect your IP address for law enforcement requirements. See their privacy page here- https://policies.google.com/privacy.  
  
We use Vimeo to display videos see their cookie policy here - https://vimeo.com/cookie\_policy  
  
We use Firebase to send alerts if you enable this feature. See their privacy page here - https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy  

CCPA  
  
Upon request, we will tell a California resident the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about that resident rights to request that we delete any of the personal information that we collected from you and retained by us, subject to certain conditions and exceptions under the law. We will not discriminate against individual California residents for exercising any of their rights under the CCPA.  

SECURITY AND DATA CENTER LOCATION  
  
BuiltWith Pty Ltd is PCI DSS as monitored by SecurityMetrics. BuiltWith data centers are ISO/IEC 27001 certified, SOC 1 Type II and SOC 2 Type II certified. Servers that process personal data are HSTS enabled, ensuring end-to-end encryption of your information.  
  
Our mirror data center is located in Australia and is SOC 1 Type II, SOC 2 Type II, PCI DSS, LEED, ISO 14001, 22301, 27001, 50001, 9001 certified.  
Our short term encrypted backups are stored at Dropbox, ISO 27018 certified data center. See their privacy policy here - https://www.dropbox.com/privacy  
Our additional backups are encrypted backups stored at Backblaze, ISO 27001:2013 SOC-2 certified data center. See their privacy policy here - https://www.backblaze.com/company/privacy.html  
Our additional backups are encrypted backups stored at Microsoft, ISO 27001, SOC 3 certified data center. See their privacy policy here - https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-gb/privacy  
Our moated backups are encrypted backups stored at Digital Ocean, SOC 3 Type 3 certified data center. See their privacy policy here - https://www.digitalocean.com/legal/privacy-policy  
  
Our data center is located in Canada, our mirror data center is located in Germany.  
  
Only directors of BuiltWith have direct access to systems which store personal data, no employee has access or is able to access personal data stored on our systems.  

ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION  
  
The personal data BuiltWith stores on you directly is your email address and short term IP logs for the purposes of fraud, security and access. You may also provide optionally provide us your address for billing invoice customization.  
  
You may performance a SAR by contacting us directly at support@builtwith.com.  

RIGHT TO ERASURE  
  
You can delete your account via the BuiltWith Pro dashboard - https://builtwith.com/compliance  

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
  
We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.  

PRIVACY QUESTIONS / FEEDBACK  
  
If you have questions or concerns about BuiltWith’s Privacy Policy please contact us at support@builtwith.com  

**PRIVACY POLICY AS THIRD PARTY DATA PROVIDER**  
  
Effective: 1st May 2018  
Last Updated: 11th January 2022  
  
This privacy policy applies to builtwith.com owned and operated by BuiltWith Pty Ltd ('BuiltWith",'we',"us',"our"). This privacy policy describes how BuiltWith deals with personal information in line with it's business practices as a third party data provider and it's compliancy with GDPR, CCPA and the Australian Privacy Act 1988.  

TL;DR;  
  
We do not provide personal information of people connected to websites in the EU or California. We do not provide data that is not already general public information. We do not supply harvested emails to Australian people or businesses.  

DATA WE COLLECT  
  
BuiltWith collects data from the Internet to provide lists that users can access via our premium tools. These lists include -  
  
    a.  Information about websites using specific web technologies (non-personal data)  
    b.  Contact information for business contacts outside of the EU and California listed publicly on 'team/contact' pages of websites  
    c.  General non-personal information about companies (social media links, telephone numbers, company names)  

The processing of data for the purpose above will be carried out via automated electronic means only.  

DATA USAGE  
  
See our [terms](https://builtwith.com/terms) for usage of our data.  

CCPA  
  
BuiltWith a is B2B data provider collecting business website information which may include personal information of residents of California. Upon request, we will tell a California resident the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about that resident rights to request that we delete any of the personal information that we collected from you and retained by us, subject to certain conditions and exceptions under the law.  

PUBLIC DATA REMOVAL  
  
You are welcome to remove your website profile via the [website removal](https://builtwith.com/removals) page.  

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
  
We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.  

PRIVACY QUESTIONS / FEEDBACK  
  
If you have questions or concerns about BuiltWith’s Privacy Policy please contact us at support@builtwith.com

* BuiltWith® Pty Ltd  
    Level 35  
    One International Towers  
    100 Barangaroo Avenue  
    Sydney NSW 2000  
    Australia
* US: 650 618 3949  
    AU: 1300 558 745  
    support@builtwith.com

* Products
*   
    
* [Sign Up](https://builtwith.com/signup) · [Login](https://builtwith.com/login)

* Features
* [All Features](https://builtwith.com/all-features) · [Use Cases](https://builtwith.com/use-cases)

* Resources
* Disable Dark Mode

*   
    
* [Terms of Use](https://builtwith.com/terms) · [Privacy Policy](https://builtwith.com/privacy)
